U.S. National Mediation Board Agreements 5806
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Union Pacific System + Railroad Company, 1935-1954 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- The Texas and Pacific Railway Company + Boston and Maine Railroad, 1943-1957 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company + The Western Pacific Railroad Company, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- The Virginian Railway Company, 1946-1959 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- The Chicago and North Western Transportation Company, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company + The Virginian Railway Co., 1943-1952 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1963-1974 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Butte, Anaconda and Pacific Railway Company, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- St. Louis San Francisco Railway Company, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Erie Railroad Company, 1950-1951 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Railroad Companies 'L', 1952 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Erie Railroad + Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad Companies, 1945-1952 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company, 1942-1952 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railway Company, 1941-1949 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- The Delaware, and Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- The Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1951-1952 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies F-K, 1936 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- The Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company, 1938-1940 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Misc., 1945-1952 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1950-1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1949-1967 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Railroad Companies 'N', 1942-1956 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Mackinaw Transportation Company, 1923-1936 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Railway Companies 'N', 1949 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Missouri Railroad Companies, 1962-1969 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Railroad Companies 'N', 1927-1934 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1929-1936 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies 'P', 1951 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Southern Pacific Railroad Company, 1949-1956 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Toledo, Lorain and Fairport Company, 1956-1964 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1947-1952 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Wabash Railroad Company, 1958-1962 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Illinois Central Railway Company, 1957-1958 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Railroad Companies 'G', 1960-1961 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad, 1949-1951 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Railroad Companies 'L', 1953 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Railroad Companies 'N', 1952 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Railroad Companies 'P', 1968 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies 'M', 1955 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Southern Pacific Transportation Company (Pacific Lines), 1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous, 1949-1951 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Railroad Companies 'R-S', 1957-1961 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Railroad Companies 'N,P', 1954-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- The National Railroad Passenger Corporation + Norfolk and Western, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- The Belt Railway Company of Chicago, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Baltimore and Ohio Railway Company, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Erie Railroad Companies, 1949-1964 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies 'A', 1950-1979 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies 'C', 1944 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Railroad Companies 'D', 1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- The Cincinnati Union Terminal Company, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Railroad Companies 'E', 1951 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Railway Companies 'D', 1949-1951 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Agreement DM and IR, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Southern, 1958-1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Long Island Railroad Company, 1947-1954 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles Junction Railway Company, 1967-1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Railroad Companies 'D', 1949-1952 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- New Orleans Public Belt Railroad, 1958-1977 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Railroad Companies 'M-N', 1957-1962 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Elgin, Joliet and Western Railway Company, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous, 1952-1966 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Railroad Companies 'N', 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Railroad Companies A-D, 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Houston Belt and Terminal Railway, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- The Pennsylvania Railroad Company (Box 47, Folder 15)
- The Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Junction Railway Company, 1959-1962 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Railway Companies 'N', 1957 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- The Long Island Railroad Company, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- The Long Island Railroad Company, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Railroad Companies 'W', 1962 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Railroad Companies 'M-N', 1957-1962 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies 'R-S', 1947-1967 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Great Northern Railway Company, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Grand Trunk Western, New Orleans Public Belt, Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Companies, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Railway Companies 'B', 1973 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- New York Central Railroad, 1958-1966 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Company, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Birmingham Southern Railway Company, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Railroad Companies A-D (Baltimore, Chicago), 1948 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1956-1958 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- (Chicago) Railway Companies, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Union, Texas Pacific, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Railway Companies 'P', 1944-1962 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Company, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Railroads Companies (M-N), 1950 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Soo Line Railroad Company, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Union, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Railroad Company 'S', 1952 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Delaware Railroad Companies, 1946-1949 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- The Virginian Railway Company, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Railroad Companies (G), 1949 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Southern Pacific + Santa Fe Coast Lines Hospital Association, 1957-1961 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Jacksonville Terminal Company, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Railroad Companies 'S', 1935-1947 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Norfolk, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Railroad Companies 'F-I', 1954 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Texas Railroad Companies, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Railroad Companies 'E', 1975 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Railroad Companies 'S', 1940 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Railroad Companies (M-N), 1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Southern Pacific, St. Louis, Southwestern Railway, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1958-1962 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Chicago Companies, 1943-1954 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Wabash Railroad Company + Railroad Companies 'D-E', 1952 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Maine Central Railroad + 'D' Railroad Companies, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad Company, 1951-1953 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- The Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Chicago and Illinois Midland, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- (UTU) United Transportation Union, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1944-1951 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1943-1951 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- American Railway Supervisors' Association, Inc., 1941-1971 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1967-1974 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- The American Railway Supervisors Association, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- The American Railway Supervisors Association, 1966-1974 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- The Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1948-1968 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- American Railway Supervisor Association, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Railway Companies (B-F), 1978-1986 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Railway Companies 'B', 1947 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1968-1983 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1967-1975 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- The American Railway Supervisors Association, 1950-1965 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1951-1962 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1949-1966 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1949-1966 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1949-1968 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1949-1966 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Chicago Railway Companies, 1955-1973 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Kentucky and Indiana + The Delaware and Hudson Railroad, 1945-1951 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- The American Railway Supervisors Association, 1947-1971 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Maintenance Supervisors, 1947-1950 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co. + Chicago Railway, 1952-1953 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Kansas Railway Companies, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Eleven Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Agreement DM and IR Railway Company, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Misc., 1962 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Illinois Railway Companies, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Chicago, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Pan American Clerical + Related Basic, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Northwest, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Pan Am, Occupational, Kennedy Space Center-Merritt Island Clerical and related, 1925-1951 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Pan American Clerical and Related ASD/ETR, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- United, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Air New England, Inc. Passenger Service Em'ees, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Ozark, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Texas International, 1980-1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Alaska Airlines, 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- When Consolidated, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Hawaiian, 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Buck's Airport Services, Inc. Clerical, office, fleet and passenger service, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Chicago Development Company - Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service, 1974-1977 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Security '76 Inc. Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service Employees, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Airlift - Clerical, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- CTE Air Cargo (Formerly Automated Terminal Service), 1981 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Frontier - Clerical, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Aerocondor Airlines Fleet and Passenger Service, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Aerolineas Argentinas Clerical, office, Store, fleet and passenger service. (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Aeromexico (Aeronaves de Mexico, SA) Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger service, 1983-1986 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- AeroPeru, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Air Canada Office Clerical, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Air India Clerical, office, stocks, fleet and passenger service, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Air Panama International Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- ALM Dutch Antileean Airlines Office, Station, and Clerical (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Bahamasair Holdings, Inc. Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service (Box 54, Folder 26)
- British West Indian Airways, Ltd. (BWIA International), 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Conpania Dominicana De Aviacion Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Serv., 1976 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- CP Air -- Office Clerical Em'ees, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Office Clerical; F and PA El Al Israel, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Ecuatoriana De Aviacion: Clerical, office, fleet and passenger service, 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Station Operations, Cargo, Passenger Service Employees and Drivers - KLM Dutch, 1952-1955 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Lanica O, C, F, and P S, 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Lineas Aereas Costarricenses, S.A. (LACSA) Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service, 1977-1980 (Box 54, Folder 34)
- Lan-Chile Clerical, Office, fleet and passenger service, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Misc., 1980-1983 (Box 54, Folder 36)
- Qantas Airways - Radio and Teletype Operators, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Lloyd AeroBoliviano-- Clerical, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Mexicana de Aviacion, S. A. Clerical, Office, Fleet and passenger service, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 39)
- Philippine Airlines, Clerical and Related, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 40)
- TAP Airlines Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service, 1978-1980 (Box 54, Folder 41)
- Venezuelan International Airways Clerical, Office, fleet and passenger service, 1981-1983 (Box 54, Folder 42)
- Trans Mediterranean Office, Clerical, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 43)
- Air Wisconsin Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger Service, 1981-1983 (Box 54, Folder 44)
- Altair Airlines Fleet and Passenger Serv., 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 45)
- Cascade Airways, Inc. Clerical, Office, Fleet and passenger service, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 46)
- Golden West Airlines Clerical, Office, Fleet and passenger Services Employees, 1975-1978 (Box 54, Folder 47)
- Metro Airlines -- Fleet Services, 1983-1985 (Box 54, Folder 48)
- Midstate Airlines Pilots, 1978-1980 (Box 54, Folder 49)
- Pacific Southwest Airlines Station Agents, 1978-1981 (Box 54, Folder 50)
- Puerto Rico Int'l. Airlines, Inc. Clerical, Office, Fleet and Passenger, 1974-1977 (Box 54, Folder 51)
- Reading Aviation, Inc. Office and Technical Employees, 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 52)
- RPS, 1976-1979 (Box 54, Folder 53)
- TACA Clerical, Office, and related, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 54)
- American, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Continental, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Delta, 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Eastern, 1983-1985 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Northwest, 1985-1989 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Pan American, 1980-1983 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Trans World (TWA), 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- United, 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Western, 1980-1983 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Frontier, 1979-1985 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Flight Dispatchers, 1984-1987 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Piedmont, 1982-1985 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Republic Airlines Flight Superintendents, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Pacific Southwest Airlines Dispatchers, 1983-1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Southwest Airlines -- Dispatchers, 1982-1989 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Texas International, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- World Airways -- Dispatchers, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Alaska Airlines, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- WIEN Air Alaska, 1975-1978 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Aloha, 1980-1983 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Hawaiian, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Flying Tiger, 1980-1983 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Aerolineas Argentinas Dispatchers (Box 55, Folder 23)
- AeroPeru Dispatchers, 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- El Al Israel Airlines Dispatchers, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Iberial Air Lines of Spain - Dispatchers, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Icelandic Airlines-- Loftleidir H. F. Dispatchers - Flight Operations Officers (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Varig Airlines Dispatchers, 1984-1988 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Air Florida, Inc. Dispatchers, 1979-1984 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- Continental Airlines, Flight Attendants, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Aspen, 1978-1980 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Eastern Airlines Flight Attendants, 1980-1982 (Box 55, Folder 32)
- Northwest Airlines Flight Attendants, 1981-1988 (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Pan American Airlines Flight Attendants, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Trans World Airlines Flight Attendants, 1978-1983 (Box 55, Folder 35)
- United Airlines Flight Attendants, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 36)
- Western Airlines Flight Attendants, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 37)
- Air New England Flight Attendants, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 38)
- Frontier Airlines Flight Attendants, 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 39)
- Pierdmont Airlines Flight Attendants, 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 40)
- Republic - Flight Attendants Airlines, 1979-1981 (Box 55, Folder 41)
- Ozark Airlines Flight Attendants, 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 42)
- Southwest Airlines-Flt. Attendants, 1983-1986 (Box 55, Folder 43)
- Texas International Airlines, Inc. Flight Attendants, 1983-1986 (Box 55, Folder 44)
- U.S. Air Flight Attendants, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 45)
- Airlift International flight Attendants, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Flying Tiger Flight Attendants, 1976-1980 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Alaska Airlines, Inc. Flight Attendants, 1987-1990 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Alaska Airlines, Inc. Flight Attendants, 1985-1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- WIEN Consolidated Flight Attendants, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Aloha Airlines Flight Attendants, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Hawaiian Airlines Flight Attendants, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Capitol International Flight Attendants, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Trans International Flight Attendants, 1982-1985 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- World Airways Flight Attendants, 1979-1982 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Air California, Inc. Flight Attendants, 1982-1984 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Alleghany Commuter Flight Attendants, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Altair Airlines Flight Attendants, 1980-1983 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Aspen Airways Flight Attendants (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Ordering from Record Center (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Golden West Airline Flight Attendants, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Pacific Southwest Airlines Flight Attendants, 1982-1984 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- American, 1983-1985 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Confidential, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Eastern Mechanics, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Northwest, 1978-1981 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Ozark - Mechanics, 1979-1984 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Pan American Mechanics and related (Basic Agreement including Guam), 1983 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Pan American, 1980-1983 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Texas International Airlines Mechanics and Related (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Trans World (TWA), 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- United Airlines, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- USAir - Mechanics, 1981-1984 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Western, 1981-1983 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Air New England Mechanics, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Frontier M+R, 1981-1983 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Piedmont, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Southwest Airlines - Mechanics, 1981-1983 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Alaska, Airlines, Inc. Mech + Related (Box 57, Folder 5)
- WIEN Consolidated, 1980-1984 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Reeve, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Wien Consolidated, 1980-1983 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Aloha Mechanics (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Hawaiian, 1987-1989 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Capitol Air Sales, Inc. Mechanics, 1978-1981 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Cross Continent Aircraft Services, Inc. Mechanics and Related, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- World Airways, 1982-1984 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- CFE Air Cargo (Formerly Automated Terminal Service) Mechanics and Related, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Flying Tiger, 1979-1982 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Aerocondor Airlines Mechanics and Related, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Aerolineas Argentinas Mechanics (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Aeromexico - (Aeronaves de Mexico, SA) Mechanics, 1978-1980 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Aero, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Air Canada Mechanics and Related, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Bahamasair Buildings, Inc. Mechanics and Related, 1982-1984 (Box 57, Folder 21)
- British Overseas Airways Mechanics, 1978-1981 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- British West Indian Airways Mechanics and Related, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Japan Air Lines Mechanics, 1979-1985 (Box 57, Folder 24)
- KLM Royal Dutch Airlines Mechanics, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Lanica Maint. Reps, 1980-1982 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Lufthansa German Airlines Mechanics, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Qantas Airway Mechanics, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Swissair Swiss Air Transport Co., Ltd. Mechanics and Related, 1977-1979 (Box 57, Folder 29)
- TACA Mechanics, 1979-1981 (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Air Florida Mechanics and Related, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Air Midwest Mechanics and Related, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Air Wisconsin Mechanics and Related, 1980-1982 (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Altair Mechanics and Related, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Aspen, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 35)
- Bar Harbor Airlines Mechanics and Related, 1981-1983 (Box 57, Folder 36)
- Cascade Airways. Inc. Mechanics and Related Employees, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 37)
- Comair, Inc. - Mechanics and Stock Clerks, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 38)
- Executive Jet Aviation Mechanics and Related, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 39)
- Florida Air Lines, Inc. Mechanics, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 40)
- Golden West Airlines Mechanics and Related, 1978-1981 (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Horizon Air Mechanics, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 42)
- Pacific Southwest Airlines Mechanics and Related, 1978-1981 (Box 57, Folder 43)
- Puerto Rico International Airlines, Inc. Mechanics, 1982-1984 (Box 57, Folder 44)
- Reading Aviation, Inc. Mechanics and Related, 1979-1981 (Box 57, Folder 45)
- Suburban Airlines Mechanics and Related, 1973-1978 (Box 57, Folder 46)
- Reading Aviation Inc. Mechanics and Related, 1981-1984 (Box 57, Folder 47)
- Air California Flight Crew, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- American, 1979-1981 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Braniff -- Pilots, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Delta, 1981-1984 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Frontier, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Northwest Pilots, 1983-1986 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Ozark - Pilots, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Pan American Pilots (File 2), 1979 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Pan American, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Piedmont Airlines -- Pilots, 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Republic Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Trans World Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1981-1984 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- United Pilots, 1981-1985 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Usair -- Pilots, 1980-1982 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Western Pilots, 1981-1984 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Air Florida - Pilots, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Air New England, Inc. Pilots, 1978-1981 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Southwest Airlines - Pilots, 1985-1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Texas International, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Sedalia-Marshall Boonsville Stage Lines Pilots, 1975-1979 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Reeve, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Wien Consolidated, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Aloha - Pilots, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- R4440, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Airborne Express, Inc. Pilots, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Airlift Pilots, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Combs Airways Pilots, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Flying Tiger, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Capital International, 1980-1983 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Trans International, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- World Airways (Pilots), 1979-1985 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Taca Int'l. Airlines, S.A., 1980 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Aeromech Pilots, 1979-1981 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Air Wisconsin Pilots, 1982-1985 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Alleghany Commuters Pilots (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Altair Airlines, Inc. Pilots, 1980-1983 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Aspen Pilots, 1983-1985 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Big Sky - Pilots, 1987-1990 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Broome County Aviation Commuter Airlines -- Pilots, 1980-1985 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Cascade Airways Pilots (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Cohcise Airlines Pilots, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 24)